Everyone deserves a great love story.
Love, Simon is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Greg Berlanti.
Everyone deserves a great love story, but for 17-year-old
Simon Spier, it's a little more complicated.
He hasn't told his family or friends that he's gay, and he doesn't know the
identity of the anonymous classmate that he's fallen for online.
Simon Spier, played by Nick Robinson.
Martin Addison, played by Logan Miller.
Abby Suso, played by Alexandra Shipp.
Leah Burke, played by Katherine Langford.
Nick Eisner, played by Jorge Lendeborg Jr..
Emily Spier, played by Jennifer Garner.
Love, Simon is a 2018 American teen romantic comedy drama film directed by Greg Berlanti from a
screenplay by Elizabeth Berger and Isaac Aptaker, based on the 2015 novel Simon vs.
the Homo Sapiens Agenda by Becky Albertalli.
The film stars Nick Robinson, Jennifer Garner, Josh Duhamel, Talitha Bateman,
Katherine Langford, Alexandra Shipp, and Jorge Lendeborg Jr.
It centers on Simon Spier, a closeted gay teenage boy who is forced to balance his friends, his family, and the blackmailer threatening to out him to the
entire high school, while simultaneously attempting to discover the identity of the anonymous classmate whom he has fallen in love with online.
Love, Simon premiered at the Mardi Gras Film Festival on February 27, 2018, and was
released in the United States by 20th Century Fox on March 16, 2018.
Critics praised the film for its "big heart, diverse and talented cast, and revolutionary normalcy", characterized it as a "classic", described it as a "funny, warm-hearted and life-affirming
tale" that is "tender, sweet, and affecting" and a "hugely charming crowd-pleaser" that is "funny, heartfelt, and truly touching", and compared it to the teen films of John Hughes.
Notable as the first film by a major film studio about a gay teenage romance, it grossed $66.7 million worldwide against a production budget of $10–17 million,
and became the 15th highest-grossing teen film and the 3rd highest-grossing teen film by 20th Century Fox at the domestic box office since 1980.
A sequel television series titled Love, Victor premiered on Hulu on June
17, 2020, and was released on Disney+ on June 15, 2022.
The film explores themes of coming out, sexual identity, high
school, based on novel or book, sexuality.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.